Hello friends,
you are very welcome to our YouTube channel. Friends,
in today's video we will talk about
how you can like a job online in ICICI Bank.
Once you add and leave it online, then
you will meet your friends in it,
like you are called for an interview,
if you do
not come within the first week or two weeks, then it is compulsory for you to come for the second interview within 6 months, from
here you will be
called for an interview, okay, so first of all let's
talk to those people at the
location, so I will tell you that
jobs are available all over India and what are the functions here,
what are the job positions, see here there is
retail banking, after that you have phone
banking, okay now in a small way I just
told you that
jobs are available here in India, so for that too
you will get a job in SBI Bank, especially in any category,
you can come to our website w.com,
after this friends you will get Gas Limited, you will get
jobs of every bank here,
you can see in any step,
bank related information job
Information guidance if you want to see
then subscribe to our channel, you
cannot join the face,
you can subscribe by clicking here
and if you have not subscribed to the channel then
you will get a job interview, after that
different banks Kotak Mahindra Bank and
subscribe as soon as possible, so first of all
I will make you subscribe,
Abhiman Deshak complete, see here, okay
friends what will you have to do, then from here if you
use it, then you take the
youth which are different, then a
page will open here, click there in
front of you, then do not forget to subscribe,
after subscribing and subscribing,
now you have to select here, after that
you will have to click on it here,
before supplying the money matches, you will
see that look opposite, if you
try the money then in this you need an
item information will come there, your
education qualification, everything will be
in this winter cooker, it will come next, it is clear
that she is the national president, then she is the ruling
actress, then her and in the last
entry has been appointed here, everything will be done,
so you should subscribe like this
So after that some such page will open
where you have to subscribe to upload the photo,
after that you have to
click on subscribe tab to click
here, if you
want to see the complete information of the subscribe then you can comment me
because see if you open the play store and
fill the declaration form,
okay after that friends you will
go to profile and also go to supplementary
information, so to fill this
friends it will take approximately one hour
of your time, so rear that now I have done
this indifference, if you
want expert film video then you can comment me, so what
we have to do is here,
see here
subscribe appointed, as if you click here then it will
start automatically here, there is
no problem in that, again
see here, the appointed voice is
not getting the job from everyone, then you
can go to that India and click on it,
this is please locations, now you
can search here by using the location trace, then
you will see from
which location you have  It is available here,
so friends, we go to cross India here and
here for demo I will show you by
taking a job, this is for sending
and if I clicked here then it is in
front of me, it opens here and if you want home then you
cannot do it like this then click here, so
here this subscribe button with which you had
connected here, all that has been done, so if you
like this video then like,
share and
subscribe, thank you.